<?xml version="1.0"?>
<root>
    <message>Request Successful</message>
    <id>P7CZW0</id>
    <nameDisplay>Sassy Lassie</nameDisplay>
    <description>This is our third collaboration with some of our Founders club members. A traditional Irish Red, with
        aromas of caramel, flavors of biscuit or toast. Loads of Maris Otter (British Pale) malt is the backbone of this
        beer. Crystal120 and roasted barley give the beer it's color and flavors. Very lightly hopped to accentuate the
        malt charcter of the style. Founders chose to do an Irish Red due to the timing of when this beer will be
        available to go on tap, which is around St. Patricks Day.
    </description>
    <abv>5.2</abv>
    <ibu>17</ibu>
    <availableId>4</availableId>
    <styleId>22</styleId>
    <isOrganic>N</isOrganic>
    <status>verified</status>
    <statusDisplay>Verified</statusDisplay>
    <updateDate>2015-03-06 21:59:40</updateDate>
    <id>4</id>
    <name>Seasonal</name>
    <description>Available at the same time of year, every year.</description>
    <id>22</id>
    <categoryId>2</categoryId>
    <id>2</id>
    <name>Irish Origin Ales</name>
    <createDate>2012-03-21 20:06:45</createDate>
    <name>Irish-Style Red Ale</name>
    <shortName>Irish Red</shortName>
    <description>Irish-style red ales range from light red-amber-copper to light brown in color. These ales have a
        medium hop bitterness and flavor. They often don't have hop aroma. Irish-style red ales have low to medium
        candy-like caramel malt sweetness and may have a balanced subtle degree of roast barley or roast malt character
        and complexity. Irish-style Red Ales have a medium body. The style may have low levels of fruity-ester flavor
        and aroma. Diacetyl should be absent or at very low levels. Chill haze is allowable at cold temperatures. Slight
        yeast haze is acceptable for bottle-conditioned products.
    </description>
    <ibuMin>20</ibuMin>
    <ibuMax>28</ibuMax>
    <abvMin>4</abvMin>
    <abvMax>4.5</abvMax>
    <srmMin>11</srmMin>
    <srmMax>18</srmMax>
    <ogMin>1.04</ogMin>
    <fgMin>1.01</fgMin>
    <fgMax>1.014</fgMax>
    <createDate>2012-03-21 20:06:45</createDate>
    <updateDate>2015-04-07 15:23:38</updateDate>
    <status>success</status>
</root>
